You did well, Baki.
ご苦労　バッキ
We're out of time!
時間がないぞ！後ろも上がれ！
Defense, push up!
Keep your focus guys! Concentrate!
集中するぞ！　集中！
ええい！　…あっ
Our first win this season!
今期　初勝利！
おら！　見たかってんだ 不破！　だあっ！
Did you see that, Fuwa?!
たあっ！やった！
Yes!!
Manager!
監督！
「Ｕｎｉｔｅｄ　ｗｅ　ｓｔａｎｄ，　Ｆｌｙ　ａ　ｆｌａｇ  風を受け止めて」
United we stand, Fly a flag!
kaze o uketomete
風を受け止めて
Let the wind blow through you
「Ｕｎｉｔｅｄ　ｗｅ　ｓｔａｎｄ，　Ｆｌｙ　ａ　ｆｌａｇ  たなびけ勝利のｆｌａｇ」
United we stand, Fly a flag!
tanabike shouri no flag
たなびけ勝利の flag
Let the victory flag trail in the wind
「遥かなゴールを信じて  走り続けて」
haruka na gooru o shinjite
遥かなゴールを信じて
Believe in the goal that lies in wait and keep running
hashiri tsuzuketeke
走り続けてけ
hibi yume tsumugu monotachi e furisosoge hikari yo
日々夢紡ぐ者達へ降り注げ光よ
Let light pour down upon the weaver of dreams
「日々夢紡ぐ者達へ  降り注げ光よ」
「汗は裏切らないって  唇噛み締め」
ase wa uragiranaitte kuchibiru kamishime
汗は裏切らないって唇噛み締め
Your sweat won't betray you, so bite down on your lips
「何度も立ち上がり  大地を駆け抜ける」
nandomo tachiagari daichi o kakenukeru
何度も立ち上がり大地を駆け抜ける
And stand back up again and again as you dash across the earth
「夢に終わりはないって  目を輝かせ」
yume ni owari wa naitte me o kagayakase
夢に終わりはないって 目を輝かせ
Our dreams never end, so keep on shining
「Ｌｅｔ’ｓ　ｓｔａｒｔ　ｎｏｗ  ＧＩＡＮＴ　ＫＩＬＬＩＮＧ」
Let's start now GIANT KILLING!
「ｆｏｒ　ｔｈｅ　ｒｉｇｈｔ  ｈｏｌｄ　ｏｎ　ｔｉｇｈｔ」
For the right! Hold on tight!
「ｍｙ　ｓｔｏｒｙ…」
My story...
「ｆｏｒｅｖｅｒ」
Forever...
ちわっ！おっちゃん フットボルダイジェスト　まだある？
Uncle, do you still have a copy of Football Digest?
ああ　多分な  あった　あった！
Yeah, I think so.
Found it!
I'm so excited!
お！うわおれ俺　なんかドキドキしてきた
How many times must I say?
毎度言っとるがお前たち…早くしろよ　コタ
Hurry up, Kota!
Lower your volume!
もうちょい静かに…焦らせんなって　もう
What's the rush?
He looks so cool, Tsubaki!
カッケじゃん！　椿のくせに！
Tatsumi's in it too!
たつみ達海も写ってる！カメラマン　ナイス！
Nice job, cameraman!
フフフ　こいつは買いだな達海ＥＴＵ初勝利　記念号だし
We have to buy this.
It's the edition that includes Tatsumi's first win as ETU's manager.
みんなで金出し合って買おうぜ  うん！
Let's gather our money and buy it!
Yeah!
Why are we always so poor?
なんで　みんなこんな貧乏なんだ？
This isn't enough...
これじゃ全然　足んないじゃんうん
Hey, Goro's son.
おい　吾郎んとこのボズあ？
Huh?
You'll get to read it back at home. Your dad bought one just now.
お前の家帰ったら　きっと　それあるぞ
さっき オヤジが１冊買ってった
Huh? Really? Nice, old man!
え？　…マジで？　ナイス父ちゃん！いいなあ　コタ
I'm jealous...
But seriously, what's up with your dad?
それよりよ　お前のオヤジどうしたんだ？
Is this year's ETU that interesting?
そんなに面白いのか？今年のＥＴＵ
え？俺もえらく　しつこく誘われてよ
He was so assertive in getting me to join.
Let's do it, Takebo!
やろうぜ　タケ坊！ もういっぺんよ！
Let's revive the Edomae Army!
江戸前応援団　復活だ！
Look at this flag and this jersey!
見ろよ　この旗　このユニフォム！情熱を思い出せ！　なんせ監督は
Remember that passion you once had!
After all, Tatsumi's the manager!
あの達海だぜ　監督になっても面白いんだよ　あいつ
Even as a manager, he brings us the same excitement!
タケ坊も好きだったろ？　達海！
You liked Tatsumi, too, right?
Hey... Slow down, Goro.
ちょちょちょちょっと待ってよ　吾郎
It does feel nostalgic...
確かに懐かしいけど　俺１０年もスタジアムに行ってないしさ
but I haven't been to the stadium in 10 years, and I don't know any of the players.
選手も全然分かんないし…　ヘヘ
Then just start learning it now.
今から覚えりゃいいじゃねえか！椿って選手がいてよ
There's this player called Tsubaki...
あのさ　うん？
Hey, Goro...
Back then, we were young and had time to spare...
あのころはさ　若かったし時間もあったけどさ…　へへ
But now, I have to feed my family and my business isn't doing that well either.
今は　家族　養わなきゃいけないし店の経営もギリギリだし
I just don't have the time to catch up with soccer anymore.
サッカに　うつつ抜かせる 余裕はないんだ　悪いな
Sorry.
Goro.
吾郎シゲちゃん…
Shige...
そっか　そっちも駄目かああ
I see, so luck isn't on your side either.
Yeah, they all seem to have their own things to take care of.
みんな　それどころじゃないって 感じだよ
Yeah right, we're busy everyday, too!
なんでえ　なんでえ俺たちだって　毎日　忙しいのによ
Though I guess we're slacking off for today.
ま　今はサボってるけどなフフフ…
Well, I guess it's hard to become an enthusiast again at our age.
まあね　普通に考えりゃ 難しいよな
この年で　またサポタなんて
でも　やっぱりそれ以上にさ
But, you know, soccer is just so exciting.
楽しいもんなんだよサッカってのは！
I've never felt so satisfied for a long time.
久々に充実してる感じがすんだ　俺
Yeah, me too!
デヘ…　俺もだ
アハハハ　何か気持ち悪いね　俺たちハハハハ！
Hahaha, we've become kinda creepy.
I actually forgot how it felt like until Tatsumi came along.
俺もさあ　達海が来るまで 忘れてたんだ
I'm sure they'll remember it all once they go to the stadium!
あいつらも　きっとスタジアムに来たら思い出すよ
Yeah, you're right.
ああ　そうだな　これくらいで あきらめてらんねえぜ
We can't give up! I'll try finding two or three more!
よし！あと２３人　当たってみるわ
Me too!
うん！　俺も！
This is just the beginning!
これからですウチは　これからですよ！
We're just getting started!
As PR, we need to seize this opportunity with both hands!
広報としても　このチャンスにガンガン行くべきです！
Oh, we're in the news. But our article is larger than I expected.
お　出たね　しかし思ったよりも大きく扱われてるなあ
Don't tell me you're satisfied with just this, chief.
部長　変な感心のしかたしないでくださいよ
We're going to become even bigger...
これから　もっともっと大きくいえ　多く扱ってもらえるように
And they will start to write even more about us in the future!
きっとなりますから！ なるといいねえ
That would be nice.
We can do it!
なりますよ！　とにかく　今のチムの雰囲気は　ここ数年になく
Furthermore, the team's morale hasn't been this good in years.
最高の盛り上がりを見せてます 特に選手の雰囲気っていうか
The players' attitudes... Their aura as well...
オラっていうか　そういうのが…
They're totally different!
全然違うんですから！
あ！　ああ…　そうか　ハハハハ
Oh, really?
We need to seize this opportunity to gain more fans!
この機に乗じて　もっともっとサポタを増やすべきです！
Right, I'm heading down to the training ground.
よし！　ちょっと　グラウンド行ってきますああ
Sure...
trumps Nagoya
Kota, who are you getting an autograph from?
コタは誰にサインもらうの？
うん…　ヨシオは？俺は椿
Hmm, how about you, Yoshio?
I want Tsubaki's!
ええっ？　あいつ　まだ早くない？調子乗りそうだよ
What? Already? He'll get cocky.
Then what about you?
じゃあ　テッタは誰だよ？俺は　いつでも王子狙い
I've always been aiming for Prince's.
あいつ　いっつも　手振るだけで帰っちゃって　サイン激レアだから
He always just waves his hand and leaves. His autographs must be super rare!
Kota, what about you?
コタは決めた？うん…
No... He's the manager!
あいつ監督じゃん
So?
誰だよ？ま　まだ…
I haven't decided.
Just pick one already!
早く決めなよ分かってるよ！
I know!
Huh? It's usually empty down here!
ゲ！　いつもガラガラなのになんか人増えてない？
Where did they come from?
Look, it's Tsubaki!
ホラ　椿君！わ　ホントだ！
Yeah, it is!
Tsubaki's fans!
椿ファンだ！ＥＴＵの女子サポは王子ファンばっかだったのに…
The female ETU supporters used to be hardcore Prince fans...
Kuro, you're manly!
シブいぞ　クロちゃん！
Kuroda fans...
黒田ファンだ！相変わらず怖そうだ
They're as scary as ever.
I guess winning changes everything.
やっぱり勝つと違うねやっつけたのが
And they defeated a romping Nagoya.
好調だった名古屋だし このまま勢いに乗れば　次も…
If we keep this up, the next win will come soon!
ヘイ　ヘイ！遅いよ　遅い！
Hey, too slow!
Didn't I say a maximum of two touches?
オラ！　ツタッチまでだって言ってんだろ
Move the ball around more. Let's use our heads, okay?
ボル　もっと動かせ！ 頭　働かせようぜ　頭！
Hey, Prince!
ヘイ！　王子！
Defenders, raise your voices! I can't hear you guys at all!
声出せよ　ディフェンス！分かんねえだろ！
Go forth!
Hey, how many times was that?
おい！　何度目だ　それ！
Left, left!
左　左！行くよ
Go.
You're pressing too late!
遅えよ　プレスが！
You have to properly decide whether you're attacking or taking it slow!
仕掛けるのか　じっくりいくのかその判断を　はっきりしねえと
Run, run!
走れ　走れ！
That was a great chance!
決定的だろ！決めろよ　フォワド！
You should have scored that!
That's tough...
厳しいうん
I feel that they can make it this year...
今年は　やってくれそう…って感じ
Isn't this too much? Don't they have a match tomorrow?
試合前だっていうのに ちょっとハドすぎない？
What's the matter?
何だよ？あ…
な　何でもないですふう…
N-Nothing!
Tomorrow's match is against Sapporo.
明日のカップ戦　札幌には１回やられてるからね
We've already lost once against them.
苦手意識　作んないためにも確実に　たたかねえと
I have to push them hard so that the defeat won't creep into their head.
We're still among the weakest.
俺たちは弱小なんだよ 調子に乗ってる暇はねえんだ
This is not the time to get complacent!
そ　そうだよね取材入ったり　練習見学が増えて
T-That's right...
I was getting complacent...
... just because we were featured in an article and have more practice spectators.
浮かれてたけど　たかだか １回勝っただけだもんね
Truth be told, we've only won once.
I need to snap out of it!
いけない　いけない
Prince, stop lazing around!
コラ！さぼるな　王子！
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…
な　なんか…サインは今度にしようか
This is kinda...
Let's get our autographs next time...
もらいづらい感じだしな
I guess it's just not the right time.
We have to do something to improve Tatsumi's image!
やっぱり私たちで　達海監督の イメジアップを図るしかない！
会報誌か　ウェブサイトを使ってガンガン達海さんの魅力を
We'll start a newsletter or a website to sell Tatsumi's plus points!
売っていきましょう！え…　あ　ああ
So, the content... Let's see...
具体的には…　うんと…
Nagata...
永田君え？
ホントに君って　よく働くねえはあ？
You're working really hard, huh?
Though my daughter's an office lady, all she does is whine about her work.
うちの娘　ＯＬやってるんだけどね仕事の話なんて
愚痴以外　聞いたことないよ それどころか
She doesn't save up too; always going on dates and vacations...
貯金もロクにせずに　合コンだとか旅行だとか遊んでばっかりでさあ
I see...
は　はあ…説教臭い事　言おうもんなら
When I try to lecture her, she just says that she's making full use of her youth.
青春を謳歌してんのよなんてね同じ年ごろの永田君は
And yet, you're about the same age as her and working hard in an environment like this.
こんな環境でも一生懸命　働いてるってのに
How I wish she's half as diligent as you.
一度　君の爪の垢でも煎じて飲ませてやりたいよ
A pimple...
吹き出物…確かに働きすぎかもなあ
Maybe I really am working too hard.
When was the last time I took a vacation?
最後に休み取ったのいつだっけ？
But I have to work hard.
でも　私がしっかりしなきゃ 部長も　あんな調子だし
I mean, the chief's still taking it easy...
And he still calls his workplace "this environment"...
…にしても　自分が働いている所をこんな環境って
Hiya, Yuri!
有里さん　チュッス！
あ！　…アッハハいつも元気だね　世良君
You're always so energetic, Sera.
ハハッ　そうすか？アッハハハハ　アッハハハハ！
Oh, really?
From the perspective of an ordinary girl, we could call it "this environment".
確かに普通の女の子からしたら
こんな環境とも言えなくないか
It kinda make sense now as to why I'm running out of topics to talk about with my office friends...
そりゃあ ＯＬやってる友達とは
どんどん話合わなくなるよなぁでも…
Still...
Oh, Sera, put your dirty clothes into the laundry immediately, okay?
ああ　世良君　脱いだものは すぐランドリにね
了解っス！
Yes, Ma'am!
Ah, Midorikawa. The date for the interview has been set. I'll let you know later.
あ　緑川さん　取材の日時 決まったんで　後で知らせます
Ok, thanks.
ああ　頼むよ
Oh, right...
あ　そうだ　プレゼント用のサインボル 書いてもらう人は
The autographed ball for the prize...
Hiya, Dori.
Autographed ball
Hey.
You'll catch a cold like that.
I need to get Murakoshi and...
ええと　村越さんと…
Murakoshi
Gino
It'll be fine!
あ…　あ…　あれ？
あっ　有里さん！有里ちゃん！
Yuri?!
Get a hold of yourself!
しっかりしろ！ わあ！　死んだ　死んだ！
She's dead! Dead!
んなわけねえだろ！医務室行って　ドクタ呼んでこい
How's that possible?
Go to the infirmary and get the physio!
はい！
O-Okay!
Edomae army?
江戸前応援団？そう！　サッカの応援だよ
That's right, for cheering during soccer games.
I'm the one who needs some cheering. You haven't come in ages!
応援してもらいたいのはこっちよ最近　全然ごぶさたじゃない
うっ！ い　いろいろと忙しくてさあ
I'm a bit busy lately...
Come on, have a drink.
１杯　飲んでいきなさいよあ　いや　また来るわ　ヘヘヘ
Maybe next time...
Hold on... Goro!
ちょっと　吾郎！
うん　…もう
Oh Mr. Fukazawa. What brings you here today?
あら　深沢電気さん今日は何でしたっけ？
Oh... Err...
あっ　いや　ええと…
So how's the TV I sent here a while ago?
この間　入れたテレビの具合　どうかなって
Oh, DVB-T, right? Everyone was so excited! The graphics is great!
ああ　地デジ！みんな喜んでますよ
すっごくきれいに映るって
あ　ハハハ　そりゃあよかった
That's good to hear.
I guess this is far too extreme...
いくら何でもここは　ちょっと違うか
Tokyo Kyo
Sumida District Nursing Home
I was just passing by, so I thought I'd check.
いや　近くまで来たんでどうかなって
アハ　どうも　じゃあ
Well, I'm off then.
あ…　生きてた
Ah, she's still alive.
きゃあ！何？　何してんのよ！
W-What are you doing?!
アイス　もらいに来たんだよ俺の部屋　冷蔵庫ないから
I came to get an ice-cream pop. There's no fridge in my room.
Are you alright, Yuri?
大丈夫か？有里ちゃん
え？貧血で倒れたのよ
You fainted.
You must have been skipping meals and lacking sleep again.
食事も睡眠も　ロクに取らずに 働いてたんでしょ
If you die, all your hard work will go to waste.
それで倒れちゃ頑張り損よいい仕事だって水の泡だわ
Even if you did a good job, the result's still wasted.
I see, I fainted...
そっか…　倒れてたのか
開幕から疲れが残ってたのかもな
You've been working non-stop since the start of the season.
You need to take care of yourself, Yuri. If not, I'm going to get lectured by the chairman.
体は大切にしてくれよ有里ちゃん
でないと俺が会長に怒られちまう
Yes, I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
はい…　ご迷惑をおかけしまし…　た！
I will repay you by working...
この借りは　仕事できっちり！駄目よ！
No.
今日は帰って休みなさい今すぐ
Go home and rest for today. Now.
ええ？　でも　もう大丈夫そういう問題じゃないのよ
But I'm fine now.
That's not the point.
If you stay and work,
倒れた　あなたが　働いていたらみんなが心配して
everyone will be worried about you and they won't be able to concentrate.
かえって迷惑になるのそんな…
But...
うん　無理せず帰んな有里ちゃん
Yeah, go home and get some rest, Yuri.
Hurry up and go home!
帰りなさい　早く
はあ　思った以上に厳しいなああ
This is harder than I thought.
Yeah.
Maybe we should just merge with the Skulls...
いっそのこと スカルズと合体しちゃうとか
Over my dead body!
絶対に　ありえねえ！
You're right.
…だよな　ハハハハ
They took my work away...
仕事　取り上げられた なによ　みんな　帰れ帰れって
What's with everyone, ordering me to go home?
Sorry, I'm late.
お待たせうん？
It's okay.
おう　お疲れ ごめんね　課長に残業
I'm sorry, my boss tried to give me overtime. I'm beat.
押しつけられそうになって大変だったのよ
We should be about the same age.
同い年ぐらいかな
Office workers get off this early?
ＯＬって　こんな時間に帰るのか何だろう　この差は
What's with the gap?
No, I guess it's normal.
いや　あれが普通なのか
Still, it was fun watching Tatsumi during his playing days, right?
でもさあ　達海が現役のころは面白かったなぁ
ああ　そうそうあのころは興奮したなぁ
Yeah, those were the exciting times.
I lost count of the number of times my heart almost stopped beating due to that!
俺なんかよ　興奮しすぎて　何度心臓　止まりそうになったか
分かりゃしねえようん　俺も！
Yeah, me too.
達海なら　また　あんなサッカ見せてくれるよ
I'm sure Tatsumi will show us that brand of soccer again.
That's right. And when they see that, our comrades will be sure to return!
おお　それ見りゃ　あいつらだってきっとまた戻ってくる
Yeah!
うんそれまで俺たちがしっかり土台　作っとかねえとな
Until then, we've got to build up a solid foundation, one that is able to beat the Skulls!
スカルズなんかに負けずによああ！
Yeah.
さて　仕事に戻るか　吾郎かみさんに　どやされる
All right...
Shall we get back to work, Goro? I don't want to be nagged at by my wife.
Yeah.
うん　そうね
わあ　桜！　初めて デトしたときの事を思い出すわ
Wow, cherry blossoms. This reminds me of our first date.
Really?
え　そうだっけ？そうだよ　咲いてたでしょ？
Yes, don't you remember?
So it reminds them of that...
ふん そういう事を思い出すのか
If it were me...
私の場合…
What're you trying to do?
何だよ　お前　休んでろって 言われたんじゃねえのかよ
Didn't they order you to go home and rest?
I'll do that after this.
これ終わったら　帰って寝るわよガンガン食べて　爆睡する
I'll eat and sleep to my heart's content.
But before that, I need to take a photo of you and interview you for the newsletter.
でも　その前に　会報誌向けの達海さんの写真とコメント
ゲットしないとなんでだよ！明日でいいじゃんか
Why? Can't we do that tomorrow? Though it's already April, it's still freezing.
４月とはいえまだまだ寒いしさ
I won't make anybody worry, since they all went home.
みんな帰った後ならさ誰にも心配かけないし
And do you still remember?
それに　達海さん覚えてない？達海さんがデビュした年の試合
Your debut match...
It was a night game, just like this.
あの時もナイタで　こんな感じで 降ってたんだよね　桜の花びら
The cherry blossoms were also falling.
わあ
That game, we were trailing 1-0...
その日の試合　１対０で負けてたのを　ロスタイムの４分間で
But within 4 minutes of stoppage time, you managed to score two goals to seal a comeback win.
達海さんが立て続けにツゴル決めて　ＥＴＵは大逆転
Amongst the ETU fans, that legendary match was dubbed as "The Sumidagawa Miracle".
あの試合ってさ　ＥＴＵサポタの間じゃ隅田川の奇跡って呼ばれてる
伝説の一戦なのよそうだっけ？
Really?
I figured you wouldn't remember.
やっぱ覚えてないんだ　まそんなことだろうと思ったけど
But you know, it will definitely help if the fans recall it...
And see you in that light when they see this picture.
だからさ　達海さんのえ こういう画って
サポタが　あのころを 重ねてくれると思うんだよね
That's all your imagination.
それって　お前の勝手な思い入れだろ？
Yeah, I know. The strong ETU we once knew will be back.
うん　そうだよ 強いＥＴＵが帰ってくる
そんな感じがするんだもの
I can feel it.
You must really love your job.
ホント　お前　仕事好きなのなあ…
The entire board will cheer when we score a goal.
味方のゴルが決まったら会社ぐるみで大喜びすんのよ
And when we're on a losing streak, it feels like you're attending a wake.
連敗でもしたら　お通夜みたいに全員で暗くなっちゃって
It's the only workplace where you can feel so much passion.
こんな…　こんな情熱注げて感動できる職場
There's no place like this anywhere else.
どこ探したって見つからないわよ！
So says the person who collapsed.
ぶっ倒れてたヤツが何を偉そうにそ　それは…
T-That...
No player can sprint constantly for 90 minutes.
９０分間　全力疾走できる選手なんているわけねえだろ
何でもバランスが大事なんだよ
Balance is required for everything.
If you're a footballer, that's the least you should know.
お前もフットボラならそれぐらい覚えとけ
It's freezing!
寒い
フッ…　偉そうに
Look who's talking.
椿…　次もやってくれっかな
Tsubaki, will you play well in the next one too?
Hey, you!
ちょっと　あんた！うっ！
Why are you still grinning while you're reading that thing?
また　そんなもん読んでニタニタして！仕事しなさいよ　仕事！
You should be working!
だ　だって今　客いねえしよ
B-But we don't have any customers right now.
私はね　姿勢の話をしてんのよ！そうだよ　父ちゃん
I'm talking about your attitude!
That's right, dad.
な　何だよ　コタまで
You too, Kota?
選手たちはそんなに浮かれてないよ
The players are not having an easy time.
Don't be fooled!
勘違いしちゃ駄目だかんねはあ？　何だよ　もう
What the?
Goro!
吾郎！うん？
Yama from the photo lab agreed to join us!
写真屋の山さん サポタやってくれるってよ！
あっ　本当かよ！
Really?!
I have been interested for quite some time now...
前からちょっと興味がありましてやろう！　一緒にやろう！
Alright! Let's do it together!
Hey, you!
ちょっと　あんた！父ちゃん！
Dad!
言ったそばから！浮かれんなってば！
I just mentioned...
Don't be overly cheerful!
まずは　チャント教えるよ  ちゃんと？
First, I'll teach you our chant!
Chant?
It's a cheer to support the team. The rhythm's very important.
チャントってのは応援歌だよ リズム感が大事なんだ
Don't ignore us!
人の話を聞け！
リズム　リズム！
You've got find the way to believe
「Ｙｏｕ’ｖｅ　ｇｏｔ　ｆｉｎｄ  ｔｈｅ　ｗａｙ　ｔｏ　ｂｅｌｉｅｖｅ，  ｃａｒｒｙ　ｏｎ　ａｎｄ　ｃａｒｒｙ　ｏｎ」
Carry on and carry on
「Ｔｉｌｌ　ｙｏｕ　ｃａｎ　ｓｅｅ  ｔｏｍｏｒｒｏｗ，  Ｉ’ｌｌ　ｓａｙ　“ｎｅｖｅｒ　ｌｏｏｋ　ｂａｃｋ”」
Till you can see tomorrow
I'll say “never look back”
「追い風を待って  そうｃｈａｎｃｅを  のがすなら」
oikaze o matte
追い風を待って
Wait for the tailwind
sou chance o nogasunara
そう chance を逃すなら
And if you missed the chance
「自分が風になれ　ｎｏ　ｆｅａｒｓ，  ｎｏ　ｔｅａｒｓ，　ｙｅｓ　Ｌｅｔ　ｉｔ　ｇｏ！」
jibun ga kaze ni nare
自分が風になれ
Become the wind yourself
No fears! No tears! Yes! Let it go!
「Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！（Ｓｔａｙ　ｇｏｌｄ！）  Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！（Ｗｅ’ｌｌ　ｇｏ！）」
Get tough! Get tough!
Stay gold!
We'll go!
「限界追い越せ  行け　キツイほど  ｈｅａｒｔ　ｉｎ　ｒｅｄ」
genkai oikose yuke
限界追い越せ行け
Surpass your limits and go!
kitsui hodo heart in red
キツイほど　heart in red
The harder it is the redder your heart will be!
「Ｇｏ　ｏｎ！  （Ｓｔａｙ　ｃｏｏｌ！）  Ｇｏ　ｏｎ！（Ｗｅ’ｌｌ　ｇｏ！）」
Go on! Go on!
Stay cool!
「あすは見えない  だから」
We'll go!
asu wa mienai dakara
あすは見えないだから
Because we can't see into the future
「Ｉｔ’ｓ　ｔｉｍｅ　ｔｏ　ｇｏ  やめられない」
It's time to go yamerarenai
It's time to go やめられない
So it's time to go. We can't quit!
「Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！  Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！　Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！」
Get tough!
「Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！（Ｓｔａｙ　ｇｏｌｄ！）  Ｇｅｔ　ｔｏｕｇｈ！（Ｗｅ’ｌｌ　ｇｏ！）」
Get tough! Get tough!
Stay gold!
We'll go!
tomo ni norikoete yuke
共に乗り越えて行け
Let's get through it together
「共に乗り越えて　行け  見えるか　Ｉｔ’ｓ　ｄａｙｂｒｅａｋ　ｔｈｅｒｅ」
mieruka It's daybreak there
見えるか It's daybreak there
Can you see that it's daybreak there?
「Ｇｏ　ｏｎ！（Ｓｔａｙ　ｃｏｏｌ！）　Ｇｏ　ｏｎ！  （Ｗｅ’ｌｌ　ｇｏ！）　予測できない」
Go on! Go on!
Stay cool!
We'll go!
yosoku dekinai dakara
予測できないだから
The future is unpredictable
「だから　Ｉｔ’ｓ　ｔｉｍｅ　ｔｏ　ｇｏ  止められない」
It's time to go tomerarenai
It's time to go 止められない
So it's time to go. We can't stop!
Sera, substitution.
Good job, Sera.
Seems like Natsu's back.
My name is Yotaro Natsuki.
I'll be joining ETU with immediate effect!